[Music]
you see Larry when you interrupt someone
you're telling them what they're saying
doesn't matter and if you think no no
that I I'm not saying what you're saying
doesn't matter
I'm
oh I just did it didn't I oh man I get
it now see now what are you supposed to
do shut my mouth and
listen I'm not going to take any cheap
shots against you I'm not going to do it
well of course you're not you know why
because you're a
black and the blacks they love me they
do they really do they're in amazing
people the trailer for The all female
version of Ghostbusters pop up online
last week and people were losing their
minds some people said it was racist
saying that the three white leads are
scientists and the black R played by
Leslie Jones very funny works for the
MTA people take it a little too serious
I mean really if you're going to bust up
ghosts do you want to be with a
scientist or bust
[Laughter]
driel